Check out our FREE [sight word worksheets](https://www.sightwordsgame.com/sight-words/worksheets/printable-sight-word-worksheets/) – we have over 150 in our database!

[

](https://www.sightwordsgame.com/)

Everything you need to know about sight words. We also provide articles and worksheets for parents and teachers to provide assistance with spelling, writing and reading.

* Search this website

Privacy Policy & Disclaimer
===========================

You are here: [Home](https://www.sightwordsgame.com/) / Privacy Policy & Disclaimer

The privacy of visitors to sightwordsgam.com is important to us.

At sightwordsgam.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit sightwordsgam.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Advertising.**

This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a CafeMedia (“CafeMedia”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia’s data usage, click here: www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Google Chrome or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We use third party advertisements on sightwordsgam.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).  
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in your browser. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Advertising Privacy Statement**  
This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.  
A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.  
By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

_For European Economic Area Residents_  
If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.sightwordsgame.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and contact AdThrive at [\[email protected\]](https://www.sightwordsgame.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

_For California Residents_  
California law gives residents the right to opt out of the “sale” of their personal information to third parties, including for advertising purposes. Under California law, the sharing of your information with a service provider for advertising purposes could be considered a “sale.” To opt out of the sharing of your information for advertising information, click the opt out link provided in the footer of this page. You also have the right to request from us the categories of personal information that we have shared and the categories of third parties to whom the information was provided. To make such a request, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.sightwordsgame.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). To be clear we do not share your name, contact information, or any other sensitive information with third parties, and the categories of third parties that we share information with for advertising purposes are supply side platforms, programmatic advertising exchanges, and demand side platforms.

**General Disclaimer**

The content of sightwordsgame.com is for general information purposes only and does not constitute professional advice. We try to provide content that is true and accurate as of the date of writing; however, we give no assurance or warranty regarding the accuracy, timeliness, or applicability of any of the contents.

Sightwordsgame.com assumes no responsibility for information contained on this web site and disclaims all liability in respect of such information. In addition, none of its content will form any part of any contract between us or constitute any type of offer by us. Specific disclaimers may apply in addition to certain content or parts of the site.

Sightwordsgame.com accepts no responsibility for and excludes all liability in connection with browsing this web site, use of information or downloading any materials from it, including but not limited to any liability for errors, inaccuracies, omissions, or misleading or defamatory statements. The information at this web site might include opinions or views which, unless expressly stated otherwise, are not necessarily those of Sight Words Game or any associated company or any person in relation to whom they would have any liability or responsibility.

This web site is provided “as is” and sightwordsgame.com expressly disclaims any and all warranties, express or implied, to the extent permitted by law, including but not limited to warranties of satisfactory quality, merchantability, or fitness for a particular purpose, with respect to the service or any materials.

Sightwordsgame.com hereby excludes liability for any claims, losses, demands, or damages of any kind whatsoever with regard to any information, content, or services provided at our web site, including but not limited to direct, indirect, incidental, or consequential loss or damages, compensatory damages, loss of profits, or data, or otherwise.

Reader Interactions
-------------------

### Comments

1. 

    [Caitlin](http://all4webs.com/t/f/michael5rpc6kblog) says

    A fascinating discussion is definitely worth comment.  
    There’s no doubt that that you need to publish more about this topic, it might not be a taboo subject but generally folks don’t speak about these subjects.  
    To the next! Cheers!!

### Leave a Reply [Cancel reply](https://www.sightwordsgame.com/privacy-policy/#respond)

Your email address will not be published. Required fields are marked \*

Comment \*

Name \* 

Email \* 

Website 

 Save my name, email, and website in this browser for the next time I comment.

Δ

Primary Sidebar
---------------

### FREE Sight Word Game

[

](https://www.sightwordsgame.com/concentration/)

### FREE Printable Worksheets

**Most Popular**

Footer
------

### Follow us on Social Media

Sight Words Game is also on social media. Follow us by clicking the icons below.

### Site Links

### Current Events

### About Sight Word Games

Sight words are high frequency words that should be read fluently and automatically upon sight; they are among the most common English words and many are not spelled phonetically.

© 2008-2020 Sight Word Games   All Rights Reserved
